KRISTINA RAJA RÉSUMÉ

→ Home: 613.422.9080 → Mobile: 613.293.4664

→ Email: kristinarajaphoto@gmail.com

→ Website: kristinaraja.com

PROFILE

Studied for three years at Dawson College in Professional Photography and is a graduate from Algonquin College with a certificate in Interactive Multimedia. Kristina has experienced with HTML, CSS, WordPress, jQuery, PHP and the Adobe Creative Suite.

Kristina has a strong work ethic and prides herself on being determined, organized, professional and creative. She is inspired and driven by modern influences in pop culture. Kristina is able to work well with others and can also handle independent projects. Apart from being in front of a computer screen, Kristina enjoys social networking, traveling, Starbucks coffee, cooking, and cats.

Looking for a position as a Graphic Designer, Web Designer, UX/UI Designer, or Web Developer.

EXPERIENCE

Ottawa General Contractors, Ottawa,

Intern Graphic Designer June 2014 – present

Arbitrage Magazine, Ottawa, ON

Volunteer Graphic Designer April 2014 – present

Vidrack, Ottawa, ON

Freelance Graphic/Web Designer April 2014 – present

Algonquin College, Ottawa, ON

Program Assistant

January 2014 – April 2014

Program Assistant for the Interactive Multimedia
Post-Grad students and helping & tutoring them
with JavaScript, WordPress, PHP and MySQL.

Boast Technologies, Ottawa, ON

Graphic/Web Designer July 2013 – April 2014

Ghost (Fitness) Trainer, Montreal, QC

Freelance Graphic Designer

April 2013 – May 2013

Designed three different sized icons and a banner for an app on the Google Play Store called "Ghost (Fitness) Trainer".

Client, Laval, QC

Freelance Photographer June 2011 – August 2011
Photographed a group of graduates at their prom. Clients received retouched photos and digital copies.

Client, Montreal, QC

Freelance Photographer

April 2011 – May 2011

Photographing headshots for a Concordia
University theatre student. Client received
retouched digital files via email.

Client, Montreal, QC

Freelance Videographer June 2010 – August 2010 Filmed a wedding video using an HD camcorder and a spot microphone. Clients received an edited copy on a DVD-R. Final Cut Pro was used for post-production.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Adobe Creative Suite: Photoshop, Illustrator, Dreamweaver, InDesign, Premier, Lightroom, Bridge, Flash, After Effects, and Fireworks.
- Web: HTML, CSS, WordPress, JavaScript/jQuery, PHP, MySQL, ActionScript, and Web APIs.
- Microsoft Office Collection: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, and Outlook.
- Operating Systems: MAC OS X, Windows 7 & 8, and Linux.
- Other: Balsamiq, Solidify App, Sublime Text, Final Cut Pro.

PROJECTS

Gojournalism.ca Website

A crowdsourcing website for journalists and writers who want get their ideas heard. Revamping their website in order to create a better user experience and attractive design using WordPress.

EcoBean Café Website - Class Project

Designed and implemented a website with HTML, CSS and jQuery for an earth-friendly coffee shop.

Kristinaraja.com Website

Created a modern, sleek design and a responsive website using HTML, CSS and jQuery for a self- promotional photography website.

Cat Puzzle – Class Project

Created a cat-themed puzzle game using HTML, CSS and jQuery.

EDUCATION

Interactive Multimedia

Algonquin College, Ottawa, ON. September 2012 to April 2013

Professional Photography

Dawson College, Montreal, QC. August 2009 – June 2012

LANGUAGES

- English
- French

REFERENCES

Upon Request